<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on emeQee</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on emeQee</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><copyright>Copyright © 2017–2022, Mehmet Emin Köklü; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 06:02:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emeqee.de/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AE86 Body Guide</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/ae86-body-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 06:02:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emeqee.de/post/ae86-body-guide/</guid><description>When I was browsing a book store in Japan I came across a special magazine about the AE86. That guide had very nice articles. An interview with the Drift King, interviews with female AE86 drivers and many legendary shops and their products. A short 4 page long body guide was included. It shows almost all the differences in the Japanese AE86 versions. What is missing are the differences in the rear bumper between Zenki and Kouki models.</description></item><item><title>Learn Japanese with a User's Manual</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/learn-japanese-with-a-users-manual/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 13:37:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emeqee.de/post/learn-japanese-with-a-users-manual/</guid><description>For everyone studying mechanical/automotive engineering and an interest in the Japanese automotive industry, what better way is there to learn car related vocabulary? Luckily, my classic car came with the manual, which I believe is not often the case. This one is as old as my car, maybe some vocabulary changed by now. I need to learn my car anyway, so let&amp;rsquo;s make it a study object, concentrating on Kanji and technical vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>My Car Sucks!</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/my-car-sucks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 10:18:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emeqee.de/post/my-car-sucks/</guid><description>A happy new year. As we entered 2018 just a day ago, we still have a week until we enter Heisei 30, the Japanese calendar. Therefore it is a perfect time to reflect on last year. In this post however I will only write about my car. It has been a while since I purchased it, but not so long ago, that I could started enjoying it. Here is why.</description></item><item><title>How to import a car without import tax</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/how-to-import-a-car-without-import-tax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 23:50:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emeqee.de/post/how-to-import-a-car-without-import-tax/</guid><description>I am a big fan of Japanese cars and the ones I like the most are slowly becoming classics. So when I heard about the possibility to ship a car (or any other goods) from Japan to Germany without import costs made me really excited. I had this on my mind when I decided to do my internship for a whole year. I could have decided to do a 6 months stay and finish my degree quickly.</description></item><item><title>Carland: AE86 Specialty Shop</title><link>https://emeqee.de/post/carland-ae86-specialty-shop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 12:54:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://emeqee.de/post/carland-ae86-specialty-shop/</guid><description>A few weeks ago I did a day trip to Kyoto. I took the Nozomi Shinkansen, a fast traveling bullet train. I boarded it in Shin-Yokohama, and after 2 hours and 2 stops I arrived at Kyoto station. The train reached a top speed of 290 km/h or something. That is convenient. The reason for my day trip was the AE86 specialty shop Carland.
It was very hot and humid, but refreshing to see old cars.</description></item></channel></rss>